

Shu Zhou

shu-zhou.com shuzhou@umich.edu +(734) 272 1958 Ann Arbor, MI Shu is a designer who is interested in user experience design, interaction prototyping and architecture design. She hopes to incorporate technology and design into our everyday life.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan School of Information

Ann Arbor, MI 2016.9~2018.4

Master of Science in Information (HCI track)

GPA: 3.88/4

Tongji University
College of Architecture and Urban Planning

Shanghai, China 2011.9~2016.6

Bachelor of Architecture

GPA: 4.29/5

PROJECTS

Lift 2016.9~2016.12

Individual design of a mobile app helping detect student's emotional changes and give them instant help

Ceremony

2016.9~2016.12

Client project of a mobile app for better management of participation in conference

Openair 2016

2016.10~2016.11

Web development competition Redesigned homepage for Summit to improve website's accessibility

dLive

2016.9~2016.12

Client consulting project for Domino's Pizza Found problems and gave recommendations for their intranet named dLive

EXPERIENCE

Design Clinic (UMSI)

Ann Arbor, MI 2016.9~2016.12

UX Designer | Consultant

- Designed wireframes and mockups of a mobile app called Ceremony for entrepreneur Tom Meloche
- Conducted User Research and testing with prototype

Atelier YeAS

Shanghai, China 2016.1~2016.2

Architectecture Intern

 Designed conceptual digital models, made preliminary research reports

Atelier Dehaus

Shanghai, China 2015.3

2015.3~2015.6

Architectecture Intern

Draw architectural plans, used grasshopper to generate different forms

SKILLS

Design Software PS/AI/ID SketchUp/Rhino AutoCAD Sketch/Axure Invision/Framer.js

After Effects

UX Method

Interview/Brainstorm Sketch/Storyboard Persona/Scenario Wireframe Hi-fi Prototyping Contextural Inquiry **Programming**

HTML5 CSS3 GitHub Jquery Python WordPress

